<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tealok Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tealok Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 04:14:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Authenticating with Certificate Chains</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/authenticating-with-certificate-chains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 04:14:54 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/authenticating-with-certificate-chains/</guid>
      <description>Too Long, Didn’t Read We have the means to change how the world works. We can get rid of passwords, password managers, strength tests, password recovery flows, account registration, data breaches, identity theft, and on and on. We can build something better and safer than passkeys. We can use personal certificate authorities.&#xA;What? When we deal with people, in person or via some kind of communication device, we need to be sure we are dealing with the person we expect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of Owning Your Digital Space</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/designed-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 04:14:54 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/designed-for-you/</guid>
      <description>In today’s digital world, information is scattered across countless devices, apps, and cloud services, making it difficult to find what you need when you need it. You’ve likely experienced the frustration of searching for that one important document, photo, or message buried in a sea of files. Or perhaps you’ve worried about how to keep cherished memories—like family photos and videos—safe from disappearing into the void or being compromised by hackers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Our website builds with Hugo static site generator and Mainroad theme. This demo allows you to see what Mainroad based website looks like before deciding to go with it. Just keep in mind that the current demo shows the basics, a small part of what the combination of Hugo and Mainroad can do.&#xA;About Mainroad Mainroad is a responsive, simple, clean and content-focused Hugo theme based on the MH Magazine lite WordPress theme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/cycling-to-self-hosting/_contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/cycling-to-self-hosting/_contents/</guid>
      <description>I am an avid cyclist. There’s nothing quite like the feeling of moving fast through beautiful countryside, smelling the lemon blossoms, spotting wildlife, and having the freedom to explore off the beaten path. The challenge of a big climb is exhilarating, and the sense of flying down the other side is pure joy. What I love most, though, is the sense of community—sharing rides with fellow cyclists as we challenge each other and revel in the adventure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/digital-hearth/_contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/digital-hearth/_contents/</guid>
      <description>The Problem with Today’s Digital Services Eli and I noticed a troubling pattern in our digital lives—a cycle that many of you might recognize. You find a new app that solves a problem, and it quickly becomes a part of your daily routine. But over time, it starts to change. Features you relied on vanish, ads become more intrusive, or the app demands more of your data. Eventually, it feels like the app is taking more than it’s giving, and you’re forced to find something else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/the-business-model/_contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/the-business-model/_contents/</guid>
      <description>In today’s digital age, nearly every aspect of our lives is connected to technology. While these connections offer unparalleled convenience, they also come with a hidden cost: our privacy, autonomy, and freedom of choice. Big tech companies like Google, Facebook, and Amazon have built their fortunes by collecting vast amounts of data from us—often without our full understanding or consent. This practice, known as surveillance capitalism, goes far beyond targeted ads.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
